Guide to the Seymour Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Seymour family papers
1711-1969
1870-1945
MS 440
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
51
(126 boxes, 1 folio)
This collection is made up of the papers of ten individual members and six branches of the Seymour family: the Day family, Parsons-Dean families, Watkins-Law families, Leggett-Seymour-Doolittle families, St. John family, and Howard family. The largest sections are those of Thomas Day Seymour, Charles Seymour (1885-1963), and Charles Seymour, Jr. The collection represents six generations of an intellectually and socially prominent family and through correspondence and diaries offers detailed evidence on social life and customs in New Haven, Hartford and nineteenth-century Ohio.
Seymour family
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of family members, 1945-1981; some material transferred from the Charles Seymour Papers (MS 441) and the Charles Law Watkins Papers (MS 657); transfer from the History of Art Library, 1998.
Arrangement
Arranged in eighteen series: I. Seymour Family: General. II. Nathan Perkins Seymour. III. Elizabeth Day Seymour. IV. Day Family. V. Charles Seymour (1843-1913). VI. Parsons-Dean Families. VII. Thomas Day Seymour. VIII. Sarah Hitchcock Seymour. IX. Elizabeth Day Seymour Angel.
I. SEYMOUR FAMILY: GENERAL, (1746-1851)-1942
II. NATHAN PERKINS SEYMOUR, 1801-1891
III. ELIZABETH (DAY) SEYMOUR, 1845-1900
IV. DAY FAMILY, 1711-1897
V. CHARLES SEYMOUR (1843-1913), 1869-1907
VI. PARSONS - DEAN FAMILIES, 1863-1949
VII. THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR, 1850-1909
VIII. SARAH (HITCHCOCK) SEYMOUR, 1866-(1886-1907)-1914
IX. ELIZABETH DAY (SEYMOUR) ANGEL, 1880-(1896-1905)-1937
X. ST. JOHN FAMILY, 1886-1964
XI. CHARLES SEYMOUR (1885-1963), 1889-1963
XII. GLADYS (WATKINS) SEYMOUR, 1906-1969
XIII. WATKINS - LAW FAMILIES, 1837-(1893-1925)-1945
XIV. CHARLES SEYMOUR, JR., (1918-1975)-[1978]
XV. ELIZABETH ATWATER SEYMOUR, 1918-1969
XV. ELIZABETH ATWATER SEYMOUR (FORMERLY RESTRICTED MATERIAL)
XVI. HOWARD FAMILY, 1936-1956, n.d.
XVII. LEGGETT - SEYMOUR - DOOLITTLE FAMILIES, (1860-1896)-1954
XVIII. PHOTOGRAPHS, 1859-1967
XX. OVERSIZE AND UNDERSIZE MATERIAL
XXI. ELIZABETH (DAY) SEYMOUR
XXII. DAY FAMILY
XXIII. CHARLES SEYMOUR, (1843-1913)
XXIV. PARSONS-DEAN FAMILIES
XXV. THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR
XXVI. SARAH (HITCHCOCK) SEYMOUR
XXVII. ELIZABETH DAY (SEYMOUR) ANGEL
XXVIII. ST. JOHN FAMILY
XXIX. CHARLES SEYMOUR, (1885-1963)
XXX. PHOTOGRAPHS
Scope and Contents
The Seymour Family Papers is a collection of unusual quality which spans the years 1711 to 1969, with the greatest concentration occurring from 1870 to 1945. The papers represent six generations of an intellectually and socially prominent family which included two Yale presidents as well as teachers, lawyers, prep school head masters, a Civil War general, a newspaper editor, and a sculptor.
The papers are rich in detail concerning social life and customs in New Haven, Hartford, and nineteenth century Ohio. Family members traveled extensively both professionally and for pleasure, and the papers contain interesting views of American travelers, both in the U.S. and abroad. Because these are family papers there is much in them dealing with daily family life, childbearing, and the role of women in the family, and because so many family members were teachers the papers will prove to be a fertile source for those interested in the history of education, particularly the histories of Yale University, Case Western Reserve University (at the time Western Reserve College), and Choate School.
The papers came to Manuscripts and Archives through numerous donations from family members, the most recent gift being from Mrs. Charles Seymour, Jr. in 1979. The papers now include correspondence and other material of Charles Law Watkins, formerly MSS Group 657.
The papers are divided into eighteen series with separate series for major family groups and individuals. All material pertaining to a married woman is filed under her married name, even if the material was generated prior to her marriage. The series are arranged as follows:
I. SEYMOUR FAMILY: GENERAL
II. NATHAN PERKINS SEYMOUR
III. ELIZABETH DAY SEYMOUR
IV. DAY FAMILY
V. CHARLES SEYMOUR (1843-1913)
VI. PARSONS-DEAN FAMILIES
VII. THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR
VIII. SARAH HITCHCOCK SEYMOUR
IX. ELIZABETH DAY SEYMOUR ANGEL
X. ST. JOHN FAMILY
XI. CHARLES SEYMOUR (1885-1963)
XII. GLADYS WATKINS SEYMOUR
XIII. WATKINS-LAW FAMILIES
XIV. CHARLES SEYMOUR, JR.
XV. ELIZABETH ATWATER SEYMOUR
XVI. HOWARD FAMILY
XVII. LEGGETT-SEYMOUR-DOOLITTLE FAMILIES
XVIII. PHOTOGRAPHS
Each series contains a wide variety of material which may include correspondence, writings, legal and financial documents, printed material, and memorabilia. Only photographs have been segregated into a separate series.
In all cases letters between family members are filed in the series of their recipient. Thus, the researcher will have to refer to two series to follow the correspondence between any two individuals. Whenever a letter is addressed to more than one person, it is placed with the series of the eldest addressee.
At the beginning of each series is a description of the arrangement of that series. In most cases there is also a brief biographical sketch which will provide some insight into the interests of the particular family member and some suggestions as to the wide range of subjects that could be covered in the series. For additional biographical information see The Family of the Rev. Jeremiah Day of New Preston and George Dudley Seymour's A History of the Seymour Family. Family charts, which follow this description, will help identify the relationships between family members.
Initials and Nicknames
Elizabeth Day Seymour Angel --- EDSA --- Beth
Katharine Seymour Parsons Dean --- --- Katie
Lee Maltbie Dean --- --- Sebastian
Clara M. Hitchcock --- ---- Kittie
James Merriam Howard, Jr. --- --- Jim
James Merriam Howard, III --- --- Jerry
Sarah Seymour Howard --- SSH --- Sally
Harriet Day Parsons --- HDP --- Hallie
William Cheney Parsons --- --- Will
George St. John --- --- Clargo
George St. John, Jr. --- --- Jim
Charles Seymour (1885-1963) --- CS --- Charlie
Elizabeth Atwater Seymour --- EAS --- Betsey
Gladys Watkins Seymour --- GWS ---
Sarah Hitchcock Seymour --- SSH --- Sadie
Thomas Day Seymour --- TDS --- Tom
Charles Law Watkins --- --- Law
1981 ADDITION
4' (10 boxes), 1843-1933
The Seymour Family Papers Add. 1981, housed in ten boxes and spanning the years from 1843 to 1933, was donated to Yale University in 1981 by Seymour St. John.
The original collection is divided into eighteen series and this addition is arranged in the same manner as the larger collection. All correspondence, therefore, is filed in the series of the recipient of the letters. Letters written to Thomas Day Seymour, for example, are found in Series VII, while those written by him to other family members are located in the appropriate series. Please refer to the introductions to each series in the register to the Seymour Family Papers for additional information. The add. 1981 contains material for ten series, but the bulk of the correspondence and other papers are found in THOMAS DAY SEYMOUR, SARAH (HITCHCOCK) SEYMOUR, and ST. JOHN FAMILY.
The add. 1981 fills several important gaps in the Seymour Family Papers. These papers focus on the family of Thomas Day Seymour. The chief correspondents and recipients of letters are Thomas Day Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour, and their three children, Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John, and Charles Seymour (1885-1963).
The single most important correspondent is Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John. Clara's college years at Bryn Mawr are well documented. Letters written by Clara from college to her family fill folders 37-58 of Series VII. The correspondence covers her freshman, junior, and senior years at college. (Letters from her parents, sister Elizabeth, and brother Charles to her are found in Series X.) After graduation Clara and her sister travelled to Europe in the company of their uncle Charles Seymour (1843-1913). Sixty letters written by the two young women between June and September 1900 describe this exciting journey. See Series VII folders 11-12, 58-61. The same series also contains several letters written by Clara and her mother from Italy in 1903.
Clara married George St. John in June 1906 and correspondence in Series VII folders 64-68, and Series VIII, folder 115, describes their honeymoon in pastoral New Hampshire and George's experiences teaching at the Adirondack-Florida School. In a letter to her parents written September 6, 1909 from Windsor, Vermont, Clara describes a visit to the home of sculptor Augustus Saint-Gaudens and recounts his problems designing a new $20 gold piece. The Adirondack-Florida School was located at Rainbow Lake in Franklin County, New York and Coconut Grove, Florida. The bride who was accustomed to the amenities of life had to adjust to living in a primitive cabin in the Adirondack woods. Moreover, when the headmaster became ill in early October, Clara took over his teaching assignments.
In one particularly significant group of letters in Series VIII, folders 116-119, Clara St. John relates the difficulties endured by her first child, Elizabeth Seymour St. John, "Betty," in her first year. Although she weighed a healthy eight pounds at birth on August 3, 1908, Clara was unable to nurse the child and the infant suffered from severe adverse reactions to cow's milk, formula, medicines, and baby food. The baby weighed only 71/4 pounds at three months and her ordeal culminated with a bout of diphtheria in April 1909. (See Series IX, folder 148, and Series XI, folders 245-246 for additional material on this subject.)
In addition to the extensive Clara Hitchcock (Seymour) St. John correspondence in Series VII, the same series contains two other important groups of letters. The Seymours' elder daughter, Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel, taught Greek from 1901 to 1903 at Lake Erie College in Painesville, Ohio. Letters in folders 13-17 cover her activities for much of the 1902-1903 academic year. (Series VIII, folder 91, and Series X, folder 156, contain further Lake Erie College correspondence.) In letters written betwen 1892 and 1894 Thomas Day Seymour's colorful brother Charles discusses his financial activities, national politics, and his brother's children. Charles Seymour (1843-1903) held strong Republican views. In several letters he blasts the Democratic party for its mismanagement of the economy. "I stood the panic of '73," he asserts on November 14, 1892, "the broken leg, the grip[pe], and the nerve exhaustion that followed it last Spring, but the election news fairly knocks me out. I never dreamed that the liars and robbers would be able to deceive the entire body of the people." Bachelor Charles Seymour in a letter written on October 18, 1893 says that a college education for women was useless. He was also deeply pessimistic about the nation's future. He mourned the decline of "the Puritan stock" and advised his brother on February 7, 1894 to keep his namesake Charles Seymour (1885-1963) "out of doors." Due to Puritan decadence, "only those will survive who abolish intellectual stuffing" and follow the "manly sports."
Series VIII SARAH (HITCHCOCK) SEYMOUR contains correspondence addressed to Thomas Day Seymour's wife, twelve folders of Hitchcock Family Papers, and a small amount of other papers. It has several interesting letters written by Charles Seymour (1885-1963) from Athens, Constantinople, and Munich in the summer of 1909. One ten page letter dated August 18 describes his journey from Constantinople to Munich. This series also includes a substantial group of letters of Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour's parents, brothers, and sister. Two brothers, John Ford and Henry Valentine Hitchcock, served in the Union armies. John Ford Hitchcock enlisted in September 1861 and served in the 18th U.S. Infantry of the Army of the Ohio. He was killed in battle, probably at Stones River on December 31, 1862. Several of his letters contain interesting commentaries on the military and political situations. Henry Valentine Hitchcock, John's older brother, enlisted in 1863 and became a chaplain. In one letter dated May 12, 1865, he discusses the reaction in North Carolina to President Lincoln's assassination. See folders 109-110 and 135-137. Several other Hitchcock letters, written by Sarah's parents, describe their trip to Europe in 1867-1868. The series also contains several folders of correspondence of school friends of Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour.
Series X ST. JOHN FAMILY contains a large number of letters written to Clara (Seymour) St. John by her family and friends, folders 155-200, and a large group of letters addressed to Seymour St. John in 1928-1929 when he was attending the Insitut Carnal in Gstaad, Switzerland. The largest volume of correspondence in Series X covers Clara's Bryn Mawr years. The letters are personal and discuss normal mother and daughter, brother and sister, and school friend subjects. Clara's mother, for example, wrote about clothes, her social activities in New Haven, family doings, and news of friends and relatives. During her senior year at Bryn Mawr, Clara was "Chairman" of the De Rebus Club, which provided a forum for visiting speakers. She corresponded with potential speakers, including Jacob A. Riis and William Dean Howells, both of whom declined her invitation.
Folders 201-220 contain letters written to Seymour St. John in 1928-1929 from family and friends. The most interesting are those from his mother and older brother George St. John, Jr. Clara (Seymour) St. John in a letter written December 12, 1928, for example, describes a dinner she and her husband attended at the home of Secretary of the Treasury Andrew Mellon in Washington, D. C. The affair was also attended by President and Mrs. Calvin Coolidge. Due to a social error, the St. Johns rode up on the elevator with the President and his wife, thus when the receiving line was formed, "Cal skipped us, with a laconic 'I believe I met you downstairs.'" The 1928 presidential election is alluded to in several letters, folders 204, 206, and 216.
George St. John, Jr., called Jimmy, was at Corpus Christi College, Cambridge at the same time his younger brother was in Switzerland. George's letters give a good view of his activities at the English university, for his correspondence is filled with discussions of concerts, rowing, skating, bicycling, hockey, the food, and the weather. Indeed, the letters of all the boys show a preoccupation with sports, especially baseball and football.
Henry Lawrence Hitchcock, Thomas Day Seymour, George St. John, and Charles Seymour (1885-1963) were all leaders in the field of education, yet little in this collection concerns their professional careers. The Seymour Family Papers Add. 1981 provides a good deal of documentation on the family of Thomas Day Seymour, in particular for Sarah (Hitchcock) Seymour and Clara (Seymour) St. John, although there is also useful information on the Hitchcock family, Elizabeth Day (Seymour) Angel's teaching career, and the youth and early adulthood of Charles Seymour (1885-1963). The addition also contains letters written by a large number of Day and Hitchcock relatives. The correspondence is personal in character and should be of use primarily to researchers interested in family history or biography.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Index to the Correspondence of the Seymour Family Papers
Acheson, Alice
Acheson, Dean
Allen, Frederic DeForest
Andrews, Catharine Augusta (Day)
Andrews, Harriet Day
Andrews, Mrs. James H.
Andrews, Julia
Andrews, Laura Day
Angel, Elizabeth Day (Seymour)
Angel, Henry Seymour
Angel, James Rowland
Angel, John
[Angell, Kay?)
Bakewell, Charles
Bayne-Jones, Mrs. Stanhope
Beves, Donald H.
Blass, Frederick
[Blauvert, Mary?]
Bonaparte, Ellen Channing (Day)
Bowers, A. Margaret
Bowles, John
Boyd, Morrison C.
Bradford, Arthur
Brewster, Kingman, Jr.
Bullitt, William C.
Buss, Elle E.
Butcher, Samuel
Campbell, Mary
Carlsen, Dines
Chamsaur, Gwyn
Clapp, Edward P.
Clement, Jean
Cleveland, Grover
Coit, Hannah (Abel)
Coman, Martha Seymour
Conant, James B.
Cooksey, Betty
Cushing, Harvey
Cutler, Francis E.
Davies, Walter G.
Davison, F., Trubee
Day, Alice H.
Day, Arthur
Day, Edward L.
Day, Ellen P.
Day, George Parmley
Day, Harriet
Day, Henry Noble
Day, Katharine Seymour
Day, Nancy
Day, Sarah (Coit)
Day, Thomas
Day, Thomas Mills
Dean, Katharine (Parsons)
Dean, Lee Maltbie
DeVane, Mabel
D'Ooge, Martin
Doolittle, Laura (Seymour)
Doolittle, Thomas Benjamin
[Dreir?], Katherine
Edmonson, Marie
Eliot, T.S.
Ellinte, Janet J.
Ely, Mary Frances (Day)
Farr, Hollon A.
Farnham, Thomas
Fromkes, Eva and Maurice
Gaillard, Edward
Garmany, Carrie
Gelat, A. Thomas
Gibbs, Josiah Willard
Goodell, Thomas D.
Greene, Jerome D.
[Hadley, Arthur T.?]
Hadley, Morris
Halifax, Lord
Halifax, Lady Dorothy
Harkness, Nancy
Hawkins, George W.
Heermance, Laura (Woolsey)
Hemingway, Louise
Hemingway, Minerva Hart
Hitchcock, Charles
Hitchcock, Clara Maria
Hitchcock, Grace
Hitchcock, Herbert
Holden, Margaretta
Holden, Reuben A.
Holley, Sarah Coit (Day)
Howard, James M., Jr.
Howard, James M., III
Howard, Sarah (Seymour)
Hunt, A. Everett, Jr.
Hunt, Samuel F.
Hutchison, Ralph Cooper
Jackson, Katherine D.
Jackson, Rose
Jebb, Sir Richard
Jenks, Marjorie
Jones, Louise Seymour
Kane, Elliot
Keep, Elizabeth
Keep, Robert Porter
Kellery, Mary B.
Kerr, Chester
Kirby, William
Knapp, William
Lansbury, Clara
Law, Archibald
Law, Ellen Atwater
Law, John
Lawton, Carolyn Fox
Lee, George
Leggett, Leverett
Leggett, Marilla (Wells)
[Leggett, Mary (Strong)?]
Leggett, Mortimer Dormer
Leggett, Mortimer Marcellus
Leggett, Wells Willner
Lindsay, Elizabeth
Linen, Joseph, Jr.
[Lovett, Sid?]
McAfee, Helen
McCarthy, Leighton
McClure, Helen
McCook, Anson T.
[Marshall, George?]
Mason, Mary
Mendell, Clare
Metcalf, Julia
Michelet, Jules
Miller, Rebecca
Monier, Helen Warren (Hall)
Morley, Eliza Melissa (Hitchcock)
Morrell, Norman
Morrill, Frank Forrest
Nettleton, George
Nicolay, Helen
Norton, Charles Eliot
Odell, Joseph H.
Otis, Philo Adams
Oviatt, Heman
Packard, Lewis R.
Page, Thomas Nelson
Parker, Horatio
Parker, Mary
Parlow, Minnie
Parsons, Barrie (O'Neill)
Parsons, Charles Seymour
Parsons, Christina
Parsons, Dorothy
Parsons, Elizabeth
Parsons, Harriet Day
Parsons, Hugh Galt
Parsons, Mary (Blackman)
Parsons, Myra
Parsons, Robert, Jr.
Parsons, Robert Day
Parsons, Sarah (Seymour)
Parsons, Seymour
Parsons, William Cheney
Parsons, William Edward
Peabody, Annie Putnam
Pearson, Lester
Perkins, Don
Perkins, William Rufus
Perrin, Bernadotte
[Perrin?], Lester
[Peters, Philip T.?]
Pflieger, Robert P.
Phillips, Caroline D.
Phillips, Duncan
Putnam, Ellen Day
Putnam, Harriette (Day)
Putnam, Katharine Day
Reeve, Irma
Reid, Helen
Reynolds, Alice E.
Roberts, W. Rhys
Robinson, Charles E.
Robinson, Clara
Rogers, Edward Pendleton
Roosevelt, Eleanor
Roosevelt, Theodore
Roper, Dorothy
Rudd, Maria C. Holley
Saarinen, Loja
Sachsen-Meinigen, Prinz Friedrich V.
St. John, Clara (Seymour)
St. John, Connie
St. John, George Clair
St. John, George Clair
St. John, Margaret
St. John, Seymour
St. John, Susan
Sandys, Sir John Edwin
Schley, Reeve
Scott, Walter
Scranton, William
[Scranton, Worthington?]
Seymour, Charles (1777-1852)
Seymour, Charles (1807-1886)
Seymour, Charles (1843-1913)
Seymour, Charles (1885-1963)
Seymour, Charles, Jr.
Seymour, Charles, III
Seymour, Charlotte
Seymour, Charlotte (Ball)
Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater
Seymour, Elizabeth (Day)
Seymour, Ella B.
Seymour, Emily
Seymour, Fannie F.
Seymour, George Dudley
Seymour, Gladys (Watkins)
Seymour, Henry Albert
Seymour, Joel M.
Seymour, Julia
Seymour, Mary (Leggett)
Seymour, Nathan Perkins
Seymour, Pearl
Seymour, Sarah (Hitchcock)
Seymour, Thomas Day
Sherman, John
Sill, Edward R.
Simmons, Mrs. Charles
Smith, Charles Josiah
Spellman, Francis Cardinal
Stanley, Harold
Stanton, Louise (Parsons)
Stevens, William Arnold
Stewart, Nikey
Stimson, Henry
Stokowski, Leopold
Strong, George A.
Strong, Sidney
Talcott, Mary Kingsbury
Terry, Milton S.
Tinker, Chauncey Brewster
Townsend, George
Townsend, Timothy Dwight
Trimble, John
Tuttle, H. Emerson
Tweedsmuir, Lord
Waldstein, Charles
Walker, John
Waring, Thomas R.
Warren, Charles
Watkins, Charles Law
Watkins, Elizabeth (Law)
[Watkins?], Jean
Watkins, Marie Bader
Watkins, Thomas Hamer
Welles, Kenneth B.
[Wells?], Harriet
West, Andrew T.
White, E. B.
White, Williams
Whitney, William Dwight
Wilbur, Philo Adams
[Wilkinson, Harriet?]
Willard, Emma
Williams, Rebecca
Williamson, Edith Ely
Williamson, James DeLong
Willkie, Mrs. Wendell
Wilson, Hugh R.
Windsor, Duke and Duchess
Winternitz, Mrs. Milton
Woodbine, Helen
Wright, Henry Burt
Wright, James K.
Wright, John H.
[Wyath, John Allan?]
Biographical / Historical
For charts outlining the genealogical relations of the Seymour family, please consult the Genealogical Charts.
Americans -- Europe; Art -- Study and teaching; Art, Italian; Childbirth; Education -- United States; Families; Upper class; Women -- Education; Women -- United States; Europe -- Description and travel; Hartford (Conn.) -- Social life and customs; New Haven (Conn.) -- Social life and customs; Ohio -- Social life and customs; United States -- History -- Civil War, 1861-1865; United States -- Politics and government -- 19th century; Account books; Diaries; Educators; Lawyers; Women teachers; Angel, Elizabeth Day Seymour, 1876-1942; Angel, John, 1881-1960; Day, Thomas Mills, 1817-1905; Dean, Katharine Parsons, 1870-; Doolittle, Laura Seymour, 1873-1957; Hitchcock, Clara Maria, b. 1853; Hitchcock, Henry Valentine, 1838-; Hitchcock, John Ford, 1840-1862; Howard, Sarah Seymour, 1920-1945; Parsons, Sarah Day Seymour, 1845-1934; Seymour, Charles, 1777-1852; Seymour, Charles, 1807-1886; Seymour, Charles, 1843-1913; Seymour, Charles, 1885-1963; Seymour, Charles, Jr., 1912-1977; Seymour, Elizabeth Atwater, 1914-1969; Seymour, Elizabeth Day, 1816-1900; Seymour, Gladys Marion Watkins, 1887-1978; Seymour, Isaac, 1723-1755; Seymour, Julia, 1804-1886; Seymour, Mary Leggett; Seymour, Moses, 1710 or 1-1795; Seymour, Nathan Perkins, 1813-1891; Seymour, Sarah Melissa Hitchcock, 1846-1916; Seymour, Thomas D. (Thomas Day), 1848-1907; Seymour, Thomas, 1735-1829; Sill, Edward Rowland, 1841-1887; St. John, Clara Hitchcock Seymour, 1880-1958; St. John, George, 1877-; Watkins, C. Law (Charles Law), 1886-1945; Day family; Dean family; Doolittle family; Hitchcock family; Howard family; Law family; Leggett family; Parsons family; Saint John family; Seymour family; Watkins family; Bryn Mawr College; Yale College (1718-1887). Class of 1870; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1908; Yale College (1887- ). Class of 1935; Yale University -- Faculty; Paris Peace Conference. United States Territorial Section ( 1919-1920. United States Territorial Section) -- 1919-1920
- Seymour Family: General, (1746-1851)-1942; Series I; 5" (1 box)
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of two sections.
  Early Papers consists of the papers of:
  Thomas Clap (1703-1767)
  Charles Seymour (1777-1852)
  Charles Seymour (1807-1886)
  Isaac Seymour (1723-1755)
  (Jacob Seymour?)
  Julia Seymour (1804-1886)
  Moses Seymour (1710/11-1795)
  Thomas Seymour (1735-1829)
  These papers consist of a variety of materials and are arranged alphabetically by the names of the family members.
  Genealogical Material contains information collected over many years by members of the Seymour, Day, and Leggett families. This material includes correspondence, lists, family trees, and texts from gravestones.
  - Early Papers
    - Clap, Thomas (1703-1767): memoirs, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Seymour, Charles (1777-1852): correspondence from Nathan Perkins Seymour, 1841-1851 (Box 1, Folder 2-3)
      General note